Product opportunity explorers, customer review insights
offers valuable information to help with product research.
This tool analyzes customer feedback
from the past six months to help you identify
valued product features and common issues
to consider when developing or improving products
in the Amazon store.
You can look at customer reviews in either niche view
or ASIN view, select the niche or product
you want to see insights for
and go to the customer review insights tab.
The niche customer review insights page
aggregates customer reviews from top performing products
within a category, helping you identify common themes
across similar items.
The ASIN customer review insights tab focuses
on customer feedback for a specific product.
For either view, you can switch between positive topics
or negative topics to see snippets of customer feedback
organized by topic and frequency.
Use both to help you identify and address trends.
For an ASIN's insights, you'll see how often
a topic was mentioned for the parent ASIN,
as well as links to child ASIN's
where that topic appears in reviews.
Below the customer review insights section,
you'll see two interactive visualizations.
The topic impact of star rating chart
illustrates how customer feedback themes
affect product ratings for a niche or a product.
Use the toggle options to compare different metrics
and analyze performance.
For example, if value for money consistently
boosts ratings, you might want to prioritize
that experience in your product design and instructions.
The customer review topic mentions trends graph
shows how often certain topics are being mentioned over time.
This view can help you see if a specific issue
is improving or not, or whether customer priorities
are shifting.
Select a topic from the dropdown and use the toggle options
to focus your analysis.
Analyzing returns data alongside review insights
can also help you identify valuable patterns
in customer behavior.
On the niche details page, select the returns tab
to view the most common return reasons in a niche
organized by topic.
In the topic returns trend chart,
select any topic to track how its return reasons change
over time.
With this information, you can proactively address
common customer concerns for your products or listings.